### Contact

+918454891988 (Mobile) jobs@couture.ai

www.linkedin.com/in/prateek2012 (LinkedIn)

www.couture.ai (Company) github.com/sprateek (Other)

### Top Skills

Product Design
Artificial Intelligence
Analytics

### Languages

English (Full Professional) Hindi (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Elementary)

Honors-Awards
Rank 1 among 1.1 Million

# Prateek Srivastava

Co-Founder & CEO at Couture.ai Bengaluru

## Summary

Technology thought leader, passionate about bridging engineering efforts with fluctuating market needs and solving core engineering issues. Highly creative with strong business acumen & experience in delivering world class products

 world traveller, all things data, Al/ML, marketplaces, mobile, photographer

## Experience

Couture.ai Co-Founder & CEO 2017 - Present (3 years) Bengaluru Area, India

#### **Ticombo**

Advisor

April 2017 - Present (3 years 5 months)

Berlin Area, Germany

Ticombo is a combined ticket marketplace for live events - by users for users

#### Adoro

Co-founder & Chief Product Officer May 2015 - April 2017 (2 years)

Mumbai Area, India

Adoro is a smart fashion network with the ultimate personalized shopping experience for women. It's designed to understand women's style, fit and price points and recommends products that they would adore.

Adoro finds products from across the web stores and relies on community curation to minimize hassles of endless search.

Adoro has the world's first style assistant which you can talk to and, just like an in-store personal shopper, ask for recommendations. Women can shop directly on Adoro and can track their orders from across marketplaces at one place.

Kony, Inc.
Technical Architect
February 2010 - May 2015 (5 years 4 months)
Orlando, Florida Area

Leading enterprise mobility company and developer of cloud-based enterprise applications and platforms designed to help enterprises transform ideas into innovative omni-channel applications.

As one of the initial hires in 2010, I worked closely with the CEO for multiple customer facing roles and assumed responsibility of setting up development centers in Americas & EMEA regions while executing global roadmaps of multiple award winning consumer products in travel, fin-tech & health-tech domains.

- Served as lead architect in design and delivery of multiple consumer products for Fortune 500 companies in various domains - Travel (Southwest Airlines, Delta Airlines, Expedia), Hospitality (Marriott International, Hyatt Hotels), Finance (Ally Financial, Citibank), Healthcare (WellPoint, WeightWatchers), etc.
- Built foundation of Kony's apps portfolio working closely with the CTO resulting in stable revenue stream and growth potential for the company
- Defined roadmaps and requirements for multiple SaaS products including product marketing communication

Verizon
Data Engineer
August 2009 - February 2010 (7 months)
Hyderabad Area, India

Joined as part of the core data science team responsible for building models for pricing/bundling of consumer plans. Developed solutions to provide insights into distributed customer sales data and create plans tailoring to customer's different geographies and preferences

Kuliza Technologies Software Developer July 2008 - December 2008 (6 months) Bengaluru Area, India

Built a platform to quickly build social websites by plugging white label solutions for most commonly used features

# Education

Birla Institute of Technology and Science B.E.(Hons.), Computer Science · (2005 - 2009)